solarimpulse.com 2019-07-12

# SOLAR IMPULSE

SOLAR IMPULSE FOUNDATION
Chemin Messidor 5
CH-1006 Lausanne
Switzerland
Introduction
The Solar Impulse Foundation takes your privacy seriously. Please read this Privacy Policy
carefully to learn more about the Solar Impulse Foundation's process of your personal
identifying information that the Solar Impulse Foundation collects when you visit the Solar
Impulse Foundation's website (the "Website"). The Solar Impulse Foundation reserves the
right to change this Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you. You are therefore
responsible for regularly reviewing this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy covers Solar
Impulse Foundation's processing of personal identifying information that the Solar Impulse
Foundation collects when you are on the Website and when you use services on the Website.
This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of any companies or legal entities that the
Solar Impulse Foundation does not own or control nor to any person that the Solar Impulse
Foundation does not employ. The Website is provided subject to the acceptance of the Privacy
Policy with no reservations. Consent is deemed issued when the Website is accessed and/or
used.
Information collection and use
The Solar Impulse Foundation does not collect personal identifying information when you
access and browse the Website without disclosing your personal data (except cookies; see
below under "cookies"). The Solar Impulse Foundation collects personal identifying
information when you register on the Website and when you use certain products or services
on the Website. When you register on the Website, the Solar Impulse Foundation asks for
your name, e-mail address, and some other personal information. Once you register and/or
sign-in on the Website, you are not anonymous to the Solar Impulse Foundation. The Solar
Impulse Foundation automatically receives and records information on its server logs from
your browser, including your Internet Protocol address (IP address), which identifies your
computer.
Information sharing and disclosure
The Solar Impulse Foundation will not sell or rent your personal identifying information to
third parties. The Solar Impulse Foundation may send personal identifying information about
you to third parties only when:
the Solar Impulse Foundation needs to share your personal identifying information to provide
products or services you have requested through the Website;
(i) the Solar Impulse Foundation needs to send the information to third parties to check
       your identity and background;
the Solar Impulse Foundation needs to send the information to third parties who work on
behalf of or in connection with the Solar Impulse Foundation to provide a product or service
to you, such as the World Alliance for Efficient Solutions, (these third parties do not have any
rights to use the personal identifying information that the Solar Impulse Foundation provides
to them beyond what is necessary to provide a product or service to you);
the Solar Impulse Foundation responds to courts or authorities; or

the Solar Impulse Foundation deems your actions on the Website as violating Solar Impulse
Foundation Website Terms and Conditions or any other Solar Impulse Foundation's
guidelines or rules applicable for specific services.
Cookies
The Solar Impulse Foundation may set and access the Solar Impulse Foundation's cookies on
your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous
unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a website's computer and stored on your
computer's hard drive. The Solar Impulse Foundation uses its own cookies for number of
purposes, mainly to:
access your information when you sign in, so that we can provide you with customized
content;
estimate and report the total audience size and traffic of the Website; and/or
conduct research and development to improve the Website contents and services and achieve
and maintain a high service level.
You have the choice to allow the Website's cookies to be stored on your computer and decide
to change your browser's settings in this respect. You can also delete cookies that have been
saved at any time.
Children's Privacy
The Solar Impulse Foundation does not knowingly collect personal data from children.
The Solar Impulse Foundation does not take specific steps to protect the privacy of children
who disclose their personal identifying information to the Solar Impulse Foundation.
Access to your Personal Identifying Information
The Solar Impulse Foundation gives you the ability to consult the personal identifying
information of your profile upon being duly identified by the Solar Impulse Foundation, by
sending us an e-mail including in the title of the e-mail the reference to personal identifying
information at [privacy@solarimpulse.com]. The Solar Impulse Foundation allows you to
challenge the data that it holds about you and you may have such data rectified, amended or
completed. The Solar Impulse Foundation reserves its rights to withhold your personal
identifying information if you have not provided a strict identification proof. The Solar
Impulse Foundation further reserves its rights to withhold your personal identifying
information if justified by its overriding interests.
Security
If you communicate with the Solar Impulse Foundation by e-mail, you should note that the
security of e-mails is uncertain. By sending sensitive or confidential e-mail messages or
information which are not encrypted, you accept the risk of such uncertainty and possible lack
of confidentiality. The Solar Impulse Foundation may use industry standard SSL encryption
to protect data transmissions.
Privacy Compliance

The Solar Impulse Foundation is subject to Swiss data protection laws when collecting and
processing personal identifying information. For the remaining, the Terms and Conditions of
the Website remain applicable.
Questions or suggestions
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy, please send us an
email at contact@solarimpulse.com.
